Guide to the Margaret Wylie papers, 1926-1963.
Wylie, Margaret papers, 1926-1963.
- Series II. Subject Files, Correspondence,Booklets, and Questionnaires
  - 1927-1928
    - Various Counties, 1927-1928 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - 1928-1929
    - Jamestown H.D.A., 1928-1929 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - 1929-1930
    - Annual Report, 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Attendance Reports, 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Club Papers, 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Club Publicity - Tie up, 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Dodger Announcements, 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Etha Meetings, 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Extension Orders, 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Lay Leader Form Letters, 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Lay Leader Questionnaire Returns, 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Material sent to Agents, 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Mimeographed Material - Clothing, 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Mimeograph Material - Nutrition, 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Miss Van Rensselaer, 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Monthly Report (Wilker), 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Notes for Future Reference, 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Plan of Work, 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Preliminary Work - a record, 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Publicity Material (conference), 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Publicity (newspaper), 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Publicity on county-wide, 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Publicity Used (Eastman), 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Refused Preliminary Work, 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - Requests for Work, 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - Resident Material, 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - Schuyler, 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - Spring Conference, 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - Statement of College Function in State Programs, 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - Stenographic and long-handed notes - Lay Leader Conference, 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - Study Club Reports, 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 58)
    - Suggestions on Publicity (Eastman), 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 59)
    - Child Welfare News Summary, 1929-1931 (Box 15, Folder 60)
    - Round Robin, 1929-1931 (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - 1930-1931
    - Plans of Work: Home Economics Extension, 1930-1931 (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - Untitled
    - Club Papers (Box 15, Folder 74)
    - Mimeograph Materials Ordered (Box 15, Folder 75)
    - Program for the Young Child (Box 15, Folder 76)
    - Reference Material (Box 15, Folder 77)
    - Various Summaries - White House (Box 15, Folder 78)
  - 1926-1927
    - Mailing List, 1926-1927 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - 1927-1928
    - Child Behavior - Marguerite Wilker, 1927-1928 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Children Magazine, 1927-1928 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - 1928-1929
    - Addresses, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Agent's Conference, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Annual Report, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Bills, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Calendar, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Checklist - Book exhibit, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Child Welfare News, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Club Papers: Unadilla - West Oneonta, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Club - Fall Reports, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Club Form Letters, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Club-Winter Reports, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Conference Form Letters, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Conference Reports, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Dodgers Announcement, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Expense Accounts, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Extension Mutings and Conferences, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Farmer's Week Material, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Monthly Report, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Mrs. Alma H. Jones, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Orders, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Original Requests from Counties, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Related Program for the Young Child, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Study Club Material, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Study Club Organization, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Toy Material, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Travel Cards, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Trip Reports, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Untitled, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Van Rensselear, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Plan of Work for Dean, 1928-1930 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Child Guidance Questionnaire
    - Conference Series Questionnaire: Batavia - Genesee County, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Conference Series Questionnaire: Buffalo, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Conference Series Questionnaire: Elmira, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Conference Series Questionnaire: Hamilton - Madison County, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Conference Series Questionnaire: Oneonta - Otsego County, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Conference Series Questionnaire: Rochester - Monroe County, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Child Study Club Booklets
    - Cornell University, 1929-1930 (Box 17, Folder 1-2)
    - Williamsville, 1929-1930 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - WestOneonta, 1929-1930 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - NewPaltz, 1929-1930 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Hamiliton, 1929-1930 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Sound Avenue, Suffolk County, 1929-1930 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Riverhead Home Bureau, Suffolk County, 1929-1930 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Southold Home Bureau, Suffolk County, 1929-1930 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Elmira, Chemung County, 1929-30 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - West Falls, Erie County, 1929-1930 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Rochester, 1929-1930 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Albany, 1929-1930 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Centuach?, Suffolk County, 1929-1930 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Cazenovia, Madison County, 1929-1930 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Orchard Park, 1929-1930 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Kevhonkson- Accord, 1929-1930 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - East Aurora, 1929-1930 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Otsego, Oneonta County, 1929-1930 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Buffalo, 1929-1930 (Box 17, Folder 20-21)
    - Oakfield, Genesee County, 1929-1930 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Jamestown, Cautauqua County, 1929-1932 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - St. Lawrence County, 1930 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Potsdam, 1930-1931 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Ulster County, 1930-1931 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Buffalo, 1930-1931 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Williamsville, 1930-1931 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Oakfield, 1930-1931 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Mothers Study Club Booklets
    - Henrietta, Monroe County, 1929-1930 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Dekalb Junction, 1929-1930 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Questionnaires
    - Cortland County, 1929-1930 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Oneida County, 1929-1930 (Box 17, Folder 33-34)
    - Oneida County - Utica, 1929-1930 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Rensselear County, 1929-1930 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Rochester, 1929-1930 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Suffolk County, 1929-1930 (Box 17, Folder 38-39)
    - Yates County, 1929-1930 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Cattauqua County, 1931-1932 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Chenango County, 1931-1932 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Tompkins County, 1929-1930 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Jamestown, Cornell Child Study Club; 1930 St. Laurence County - Norwood Child Study Group, 1928-1929 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Dr. Marguerite Wilker, 1929-1930 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Bennett High School Unit, Buffalo, NY, 1930-1931 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Oneonta, Cornell Child Study Club, 1928-1929 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Bataria- Oakfield, Cornell Child Study Club, 1928-1929 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Williamsville- Erie Co. Cornell Child Study Club, 1928-1929 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Jamestown, Cornell Child Study Club, 1928-1929 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Falconer, Cornell Child Study Club, 1928-1929 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Frewsburg, Chantauga County, Cornell Child Study Club, 1928-1929 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Albany, Cornell Child Study Club, 1928-1929 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Requests 1928-1929, Miscellaneous Requests, National Dairy Council (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Madison Co., American Child Health Assn (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Genesee, Chataugua (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Erie (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Tompkins Co., Otsego (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Cattaraugus County, Chemung, Albany (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Schenectady (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Mental Tests-Price, Eloise; Sutton, Bessie; Barrows, Robert. Jamestown, NY (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Mental Tests - Nissen, Ruth; Johnson, Bobbie; Bargar, Billy (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Rogers, Jean (Jamestown); Clark, Lonnie (Elma); Palmerton, Lillian (Buffalo- Eden) (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Mental Tests- Lease, Donald (Buffalo); Welts, Wilfred (Buffalo); Solly, Donald (Buffalo) (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Mental Tests - Bacon, Richard (Buffalo); Reingold, Sheldon; Slohm, Ruth Jane (Buffalo) (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Mental Tests- Hint, Mary Joan; Maclnnes, Paula; Kelly Sylvia Jane (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Mental Tests - Fritts, Marylin; Richter, Dorothy; Carr, Frederick (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Mental Tests - Fritts, William; Timby, Carol; Cameron, Mary Elizabeth (Albany) (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Mental Tests - Kemp, Beverly (Albany); Hutchinson, Jane (Albany); Candlyn, Donald (Albany) (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Mental Tests - Stevens, Janet (Albany); Willbeck, Ellen; Bailey, Richard (Albany) (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Mental Tests - Wilcox, Robert; Tiffany, Harold, Wood (Oneonta) (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Mental Tests - Gurney (Oneonta); Jansen, Donald (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Mental Tests - Champlin, James; Psychological Records, Dr. Walker; Extension 1927-1928 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Dr. Perkins Work (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Child Training, 1925-1926 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Child Training, 1925-1926 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Monographed Material, 1926-1927 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Expense Accounts, 1926-1927 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Miss Wylie - Reports, 1925-1926 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Expense Accounts, 1925-1926 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Result Demonstrations (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Orleans County Child Training Work Center - Albion, 1926-1927 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Tompkins County Child Training Work Center - Ithaca, 1926-1927 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Tioga County Child Training Work Center - Owego, 1926-1927 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Requests - Talks on Child Training, 1926-1927 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - 1928
    - Home Economics Booklets, 1928-1931 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - 1930-1931
    - Annual Report; Extension and Resident Rp, 1930-1931 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Reading Courses, 1930-1931 (Box 19, Folder 2a)
    - Conference Material (1 year program), 1930-1931 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Conference Material - Washington, 1930-1931 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Lay Leader Summary Report, 1930-1931 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Material for County Leader Conference, 1930-1931 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Non-Routine Behavior (2 year program), 1930-1931 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Routine Behavior (1 year program), 1930-1931 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Annual Report - Department of Family Life, 1930-1932 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - 1931-1932
    - Club Papers, 1931-1932 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Conference Program, 1931-1932 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Conference Series - Organization, 1931-1932 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Conference of Specialists in Child Care and Training, 1931-1932 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - County Leader Program, 1931-1932 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Dr. Ruth Andrus and Miss May Peabody, 1931-1932 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Farm and Home Week Program, 1931-1932 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Form Letters, 1931-1932 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Incidents, 1931-1932 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Lecture Publicity Material, 1931-1932 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Lecture Outlines, 1931-1932 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - MissC. Morton, 1931-1932 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Miss Van Rensselaer, 1931-1932 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Semi-Annual Report, 1931-1932 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Study Club Programs, 1931-1932 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Mrs. Gertrude Sculpin, 1931-1933 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - 1932-1933
    - Conference Series Material, 1932-1933 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - County Leader Conference, 1932-1933 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - County Leader Material, 1932-1933 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Discussion Tests - Dr. Waring, 1932-1933 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Miscellaneous, 1932-1933 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence
    - Correspondence - A (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence - A (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence - A (Box 26, Folder 55)
    - Correspondence - B (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence - B (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence - B (Box 26, Folder 56)
    - Correspondence - C (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence - C (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence - C (Box 26, Folder 57)
    - Correspondence - D (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence - D (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence - D (Box 26, Folder 62)
    - Correspondence - E (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence - E (Box 26, Folder 63)
    - Correspondence - F (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence - F (Box 26, Folder 65)
    - Correspondence - G (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence - G (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence - G (Box 26, Folder 69)
    - Correspondence - H (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence - H (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence - H (Box 26, Folder 70)
    - Correspondence - I (Box 26, Folder 71)
    - Correspondence - J (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence - J (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence - K (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence - K (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence - K (Box 26, Folder 72)
    - Correspondence - L (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence - L (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence - L (Box 26, Folder 73)
    - Correspondence - M (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence - M (Box 26, Folder 75)
    - Correspondence - Mc (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence - Mc (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence - N (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence - N (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence - N (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence - O (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence - O (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence - O (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence - P (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence - P (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence - P (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence - P (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence - Q (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence - R (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence - R (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence - R (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence - Mr. Montgomery Robinson, 1939-1940 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence - Miss Rose (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence - Miss Rose, 1939-1940 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence - Mrs. Roskelly (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence - Mrs. Roskelly, 1938-1939 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence - S (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence - S (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence - S (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence - S (Box 26, Folder 44)
    - Correspondence - S (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence - L.R. Simons, 1939-1940 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence - Mrs. Kathleen Small (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence - Mrs. Kathleen Small, 1938-1939 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence - Dr. Ruby Green Smith (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence - Dr. Ruby Green Smith, 1939-1940 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence - Mrs. Harriet Stocking (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence - Mrs. Harriet Stocking (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence - T (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence - T (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence - T (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence - U (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence - U (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence - V (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence - V (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence - V (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence - V (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence - W (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence - W (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence - W (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence - W (Box 26, Folder 53)
    - Correspondence - W (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence - Mrs. Wood, 1931-1934 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence - Miss Orrilla Wright (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence - Miss Orrilla Wright, 1938-1939 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence - X,Y,Z (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence - X,Y,Z (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence - X,Y (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - County Correspondence
    - Allegany County (Box 15, Folder 63)
    - Cattaragus County (Box 15, Folder 64)
    - Chenango County (Box 15, Folder 65)
    - Jefferson County (Box 15, Folder 66)
    - Ontario County (Box 15, Folder 67)
    - Orleans County (Box 15, Folder 68)
    - Qswego County (Box 15, Folder 69)
    - Sullivan County (Box 15, Folder 70)
    - Tiago County (Box 15, Folder 71)
    - Warren County (Box 15, Folder 72)
    - Wyoming County (Box 15, Folder 73)
  - 1933-1935
    - Memos - Miss Fowler, 1940-1941 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Memos - Miss Fowler (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Memos - Miss Henry, 1940-1941 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Memos - Miss Rose (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Memos - Director L.R. Simons, 1940-1941 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Memos - Mrs. Harriet Stocking, 1939-1940 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Memos - Mrs. Harriet Stocking, 1940-1941 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Memos - Mrs. Waring, 1940-1941 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Packet Correspondence, 1938-1939 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Child Development and Parent Education Conference, 1933-1934 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Miss McDermand, 1933-1934 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Prof. Robinson - College of Agriculture, 1933-1934 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Form Letters, 1933-1935 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Miss Henry, 1933-1935 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Miss Morton, 1933-1935 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Requests for miscellaneous talks, 1933-1935 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Miss Rose, 1933-1935 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Letter Series of Child Guidance, 1933-1935 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Mrs. Small, 1933-1935 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Mrs. Smith, 1933-1935 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Dr. Andrus and Miss Peabody, 1934-1935 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Mrs. Small - publicity on lectures, 1934-1935 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Mrs. Stocking -, 1933-1935 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - May conference material I, 1934-1935 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - May conference material II, 1934-1935 (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Preschool Blind - May conference, 1934-1935 (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - NYS Nursery School Conference - Albany, 1933-1935 (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Child Development Conference - questionnaires, 1933-1934 (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - Annual Extension Conference, 1933-1935 (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - Conferences and Conventions concerning Child Development and Parent Education (programs), 1933-1935 (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - Child Development Conference (registration forms), 1933-1935 (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - Club papers sent in by the study clubs (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - Dr. Wylie's Yearly Calendar, 1933-1935 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Extension Course in child development and parent education, 1933-1934 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Farm and Home Week program, 1933-1935 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Exhibits: toys, books, slides, 1933-1935 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Book list: exhibit copies; office copies (sent to library), 1933-1934 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Extension newsletter, "The Farmer's Wife", 1934-1935 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - College of Home Economics publication, "Findings", 1934 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Information regarding young people's organizations (Girls' and Boys' Clubs of America, Cub Scouts, Brownies, Campfire Girls), 1933-1934 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Magazine list for children and adults, 1933-1934 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous newspaper articles, 1933-1934 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Nursery school programs, 1933-1934 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Publicity material on county-wide meetings - Sent in by counties - Sent to Mrs. Small, 1933-1934 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Samples of observation notes taken by students, 1933-1934 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Observation notes of nursery school children, taken by Dr. Wylie; on eating, 1933-1934 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Information regarding Parent-Teacher Associations, 1933-1934 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Radio talks - Dr. Wylie, 1933-1934 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Plans and equipment needed for new building, 1933-1934 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Plans of work - Extension study courses, 1933-1934 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Plans of work - Extension study courses, 1934-1935 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Work plans - Extension Service in Home Economics, 1934-1935 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Parent Education Newsletter - State Education Department, Albany, 1934-1935 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Reports from Department of Family Life at Cornell, 1933-1934 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Reports of committee meetings, conferences and discussions, 1933-1935 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Monthly reports, 1933-1935 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Project reports from counties, 1934-1935 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Trip reports, 1933-1935 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Questionnaire - Child Guidance letter series, 1933-1934 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Copies of questionnaires filled out by Dr. Wylie, 1933-1934 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Summary of questionnaire used at Conference Series, 1933-1934 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Summer School (Department of Family Life), 1934 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Requests from agents for work in child development, 1933-1935 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - 1935 Annual Extension report - Child Development, Parent Education and Family Life (Dec. 1934 - Nov. 1935)1935 Summary of annual report1934 Summary of annual report, Family Life Education (Oct. 1, 1934- Nov. 30, 1935), 1934-1935 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - County leader material, 1933-1934 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Child development research at Cornell, 1934-1935 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Conference series on child development - First-year program, 1933-1934 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - 1935-1936
    - Form letters - Monthly letters to study clubs, 1935-1936 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Monthly newsletter to home demonstration agents, 1935-1936 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Programs - Conferences, conventions and meetings - Dr. Manniche visit; Regional Extension Conference of the Northeastern States; Conference on youth employment in Cortland, Madison, Monroe and Oswego Counties, 1935-1936 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Child Development and Parent Education Conferences (Family Life), 1935-1936 (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Margaret Wylie's letter series on child guidance, 1935-1936 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - County and Study Club leaders' materials: records, organization, program outlines and guides, 1935-1936 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Cornell Child Study Program and Summer Courses
    - Study Club: Cornell Child Study Program (1 of 2) Syllabi, outlines, 1930-1935 (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Study Club: Cornell Child Study Program (2 of 2) Syllabi / guides; record book; comment sheets, 1930-1935 (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Summer Session: Family Life 101 (Dr. Wylie), 1934 (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - Summer Session: Family Life 101, 150, 214 (Dr. Wylie) (1 of 2), 1935 (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - Summer Session: Family Life 101, 150, 214 (Dr. Wylie) (2 of 2), 1935 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - 1936-1937
    - Annual Extension Conference, 1936-1937 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Annual Extension Report - Family Life Department / Household Management Dept., 1936-1937 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Dr. Wylie's calendar; program dates and schedules, 1936-1937 (Box 22, Folder 3)